<!--
darc, the Durham Adaptive optics Real-time Controller.
Copyright (C) 2010 Alastair Basden.

This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as
published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the
License, or (at your option) any later version.

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU Affero General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<displayset date="09/09/18 22:45:09/18/09">
<plot pos="(0,0)" size="(192, 149)" show="0"><mangle>
data="""Information about darcplot:

If you right-click on a plot, a (detatchable) toolbar appears.
Since this is a plot window, you can try it now.
This allows you to do several important things:
1. Subscribe to different telemetry streams at different
   decimation rates.
2. Select different plot configuration files (next to the
   activate button).
3. Develop your own plot configuration (in the text box area
   in the bottom right hand corner).
4. Load and save data or plot configurations.
5. Add overlays to your plot (only for 2D data in fast mode).
6. Spawn a new instance of darcplot.
7. Information about current frame numbers and timestamps.

If you have a directory with your own plot configurations in, you
can start darcplot with -c /path/to/your/plots/
You can also start darcplot by giving the name of a plot configuration
file on the command line.
Or you can start it with a telemtry stream name and optional decimation.
When doing this, you can also provide some text to go into the text box
area, so that you can do simple things with your data.

Some examples:
darcplot plotMine.xml
darcplot rtcPxlBuf 100
darcplot rtcPxlBuf 10 -m "data.shape=128,128;fast=1"

Plenty of other things are possible too.

The default plots give a few ways of viewing data for a fairly
straightforward system.  If you have a more complicated system
you will need to create your own plot configuration files, for
example if camera pixels are interleaved in your data stream.
"""
tbNames=[]
title="Information"</mangle>
<sub>[('rtcStatusBuf', 1, 25)]</sub>
</plot>
</displayset>
